Open menu

* Notifications
    
    * Back to menu
    * Back to menu
* Support
    * Back to menu
* Communities
    * Back to menu
* Learn
    * Back to menu
*   World \[$\]
    
    Back to menu
    
    Europe
    
    *  [ Deutschland \[€\]](#)
        
    *  [ España \[€\]](#)
        
    *  [ France \[€\]](#)
        
    *  [ Ireland \[€\]](#)
        
    *  [ Italia \[€\]](#)
        
    *  [ Nederland \[€\]](#)
        
    *  [ Polska \[PLN\]](#)
        
    *  [ Portugal \[€\]](#)
        
    *  [ United Kingdom \[£\]](#)

    America
    
    *  [ Canada (en) \[$\]](#)
        
    *  [ Canada (fr) \[$\]](#)
        
    *  [ United States \[$\]](#)
        
    *  [ América Latina \[$\]](#)

    Africa
    
    *  [ Maroc \[Dhs\]](#)
        
    *  [ Sénégal \[FCFA\]](#)
        
    *  [ Tunisie \[DT\]](#)

    Oceania
    
    *  [ Australia \[A$\]](#)

    Asia
    
    *  [ Singapore \[S$\]](#)
        
    *  [ Asia \[US$\]](#)
        
    *  [ India \[₹\]](#)

    World
    
    *  [ World \[$\]](#)
        
    *  [ World \[€\]](#)

Open login menu

Welcome to OVHcloud.

Log in to order, manage your products and services, and track your orders.

    * Back to menu
        
        * Back to menu
            
        * Products [Discover our dedicated servers](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/)
            
            * [Rise Servers](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/rise/) The most affordable bare-metal servers offered by OVHcloud
            * [Advance Servers New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/advance/) Versatile servers for small and medium businesses.
            * [Game Servers New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/game/) For video games and streaming platforms.
            * [Storage Servers](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/storage/) Servers for archiving, backup, and distributed storage.
            * [Scale Servers New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/scale/) Specifically designed for complex, high-resilience infrastructures.
            * [High Grade Servers New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/high-grade/) The most powerful servers, optimised for critical loads.
            * [Operating systems and applications](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/os/) Operating systems and applications adapted to your needs
            * [Dedicated server availability by region New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/regions-availability/) The availability of our servers in various regions around the world
        * Use cases
            
            * Grid computing New
            * Virtualisation and containerisation
            * Website Business Application
            * Hyperconverged Infrastructure
            * Software Defined Storage
            * Big Data and Analytics
            * Archiving and Backup
            * AI, Machine Learning & Deep learning
            * Database
            * Gaming
        * Back to menu
            
        * Eco Dedicated Servers [Explore our Dedicated Servers](https://eco.ovhcloud.com/en/about/)
            
            * [Kimsufi Servers](https://eco.ovhcloud.com/en/kimsufi/) Low-cost servers to get you started
            * So you Start Servers A range of dedicated servers that are perfect for startups and very small businesses
            * [Rise Servers](https://eco.ovhcloud.com/en/rise/) Tried-and-tested Intel and AMD platforms for competitive performance and price
            * [Operating systems and distributions](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/os/) Find the versions compatible with your Eco server
        * Back to menu
            
        * VPS - Virtual Private Servers
            
            * [VPS New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/vps/) New VPS — with twice the cores — at the most competitive price on the market! Based on AMD EPYC platforms.
            * [Distributions and licences](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/vps/os/) See all our distributions and licences
        * Back to menu
            
        * Managed Bare Metal
            
            * Managed Bare Metal Essentials powered by VMware® Your virtual infrastructure managed by OVHcloud
        * Back to menu
            
        * Storage and backup Explore all our solutions
            
            * [Enterprise File Storage](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/enterprise-file-storage/) Fully managed file storage based on NetApp ONTAP Select
            * [HA-NAS](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/nas-ha/) Centralised storage or backup space for your file data
            * Cloud Disk Array A scalable storage solution based on CEPH technology
            * [Veeam Enterprise Plus](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/veeam-enterprise/) The ultimate solution for protecting your data in a way that fits your needs
            * [HYCU for OVHcloud](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/hycu/) Simplify the backup and migration of your Nutanix workloads
        * Use cases
            
        * Back to menu
            
        * Network
            
            * [Additional IP](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/additional-ip/) Assign and move dynamic IP addresses from one service to another
            * [OVHcloud Load Balancer](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/load-balancer/) Balance your application load across multiple backend servers
            * [Private Network (vRack)](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/vrack/) Connect all your OVHcloud services together with an isolated private network
            * [OVHcloud Link Aggregation](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/ovhcloud-link-aggregation/) Get a redundant, high-bandwith private network
            * [OVHcloud Connect](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/ovhcloud-connect/) Connect your datacentre to OVHcloud
            * [Public Bandwith](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/bandwidth/) Upgrade your default guaranteed bandwidth
            * [Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP)](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/byoip/) Bring your IP addresses and simplify your migration to OVHcloud
        * Back to menu
            
        * Network Security
            
            * [Anti DDoS infrastructure](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/security/anti-ddos/) Keep your infrastructures protected against DDoS attacks
            * [Game DDoS Protection](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/security/game-ddos-protection/) Protect your gaming and e-sport business with best-in-class security solution
            * [DNSSEC](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/domains/dnssec/) Protect your data from DNS cache poisoning
            * SSL Gateway Simplest way to enable security on your webpage. Without any effort!
    * Identity, Security & Operations
        * Back to menu
        * Identity, Security & Operations
            
        * Identity, Security & Operations
            
            * Identity and Access Management (IAM) Secure your access management and enhance your productivity
            * Logs Data Platform Complete platform to collect, store and view your logs
            * Service Logs Monitor your cloud environment’s performance and security
        * Back to menu
            
        * Bare Metal Pod
            
            * [Process underway to obtain SecNumCloud qualification for Bare Metal Pod](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/secnumcloud/) Bare Metal performance in a SecNumCloud compliant sovereign environment.
        * Use Cases
            
    * Back to menu
        
        * Back to menu
            
        * Domain names
            
            * [Find your domain name](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/domains/) Find the domain name that matches your brand in one click
            * [Transfer your domain name](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/domains/domain-transfer/) Easily transfer your domain name to OVHcloud
            * [Renew your domain name](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/domains/domain-renew/) Renew your domain name at any time, for a duration of one year or more
            * [Domain name for resale](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/domains/aftermarket/) Buy a domain name on the secondary market with OVHcloud
            * [Domain name extension prices](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/domains/tld/) Find all domain extensions and their prices
        * Quick Access
            
        * Back to menu
            
        * Web Hosting
            
            * [Starter web hosting](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/starter-offer/) All-in-one web hosting to easily get started
            * [Personal web hosting](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/personal-offer/) Web hosting for your personal projects
            * [Professional web hosting](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/professional-offer/) Professional web hosting made easy
            * [Performance web hosting](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/performance-offer/) Website and e-commerce hosting with limitless possibilities
            * [Essential options](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/options/) A range of options to customise and improve your website
            * [Compare our web hosting plans](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/compare/) Compare all our website hosting solutions
        * Quick Access
            
        * Back to menu
            
        * Emails
            
            * [Hosted Exchange](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/emails/hosted-exchange/) Microsoft Exchange email and your data hosted at OVHcloud
            * [Private Exchange](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/emails/private-exchange/) Microsoft Exchange email and your data hosted at OVHcloud on an infrastructure dedicated to your business
            * [All our email solutions](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/emails/) Compare all our email solutions.
        * Back to menu
            
        * Essential options
            
            * [SSL Certificates](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/options/ssl/) Secure your website with our SSL certificates
            * [CDN (Content Delivery Network)](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/options/cdn/) Boost your website performance and reduce page loading times
            * [Start SQL](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/options/start-sql/) Add unitary databases to your web hosting plan
            * [Web Cloud Databases](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-cloud/databases/) Choose our SQL and NoSQL database service, which offers guaranteed resources and can be accessed via a public network
            * [Boost Option](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/web-hosting/options/boost/) Handle traffic spikes automatically and temporarily with our superfast Performance Hosting
    * Identity, Security & Operations
        * Back to menu
        * Identity, Security & Operations
            
        * Identity, Security & Operations
            
            * Identity and Access Management (IAM) Secure your access management and enhance your productivity
            * Logs Data Platform Complete platform to collect, store and view your logs
            * Service Logs Monitor your cloud environment’s performance and security
    * Back to menu
        
        * Back to menu
            
        * Public Cloud Discover Public Cloud
            
            * [Service ecosystem](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/) Automate your setup, propel your business
            * [Pricing](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/prices/) View our simple, accessible pricing
            * [Public Cloud free trial](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/free-trial/) Try out our solutions at no cost
            * [Savings Plans New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/savings-plan/) Opt for a 1 to 36 month subscription and save on your Public Cloud resources.
            * [The advantages of the Public Cloud solution](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/why-ovh-public-cloud/) Discover cloud computing solutions to meet your needs
            * [Cloud Computing](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/cloud-computing/) Find out more about this growing practice
            * [Certification & compliance](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/compliance/) Explore how OVHcloud builds trusted solutions
            * [Availability by region](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/regions-availability/) Explore our catalogue coverage by region
            * [Local Zones New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/about-us/global-infrastructure/local-zone/) Deploy cloud services closer to your users
            * Our documentation Read our guides and tutorials
        * Back to menu
            
        * Compute [Explore all our Compute products](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/compute/)
            
            * [Virtual Machine Instances](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/virtual-instances/) Get versatile instances that can be adapted to suit all your needs.
            * [Cloud GPU](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/gpu/) Speed up your workloads with high-performance GPU instances.
            * [Metal Instances](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/metal-instances/) Combine the power of Bare Metal with cloud automation
            * Our documentation Browse our documentation for the Compute range
            * En route to PaaS Focus on your applications & become more competitive
            * [Local Zone New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/about-us/global-infrastructure/local-zone/) Deploy cloud services closer to your users
        * Back to menu
            
        * Storage Explore all our Storage products
            
            * [Block Storage](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/block-storage/) Create storage volumes, which can be used as additional disks
            * [Object Storage](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/object-storage/) Get unlimited on-demand storage, accessible via the S3 API
            * [Cold Archive](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/cold-archive/) Get long-term archiving at the best price
            * [Local Zone New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/about-us/global-infrastructure/local-zone/) Deploy cloud services closer to your users
            * Our documentation Browse our documentation for the Storage range
        * Back to menu
            
        * Network Explore all our Network products
            
            * [Private Network](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/private-network/) Deploy private networks via the OVHcloud vRack
            * [Load Balancer](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/load-balancer/) Manage variable traffic by spreading it across multiple resources
            * [Floating IP](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/floating-ip/) Assign and move your public IP from one service to another
            * [Gateway](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/gateway/) Manage a single connection point between your private network & internet
            * Our documentation View our documentation for the Network range
        * Back to menu
            
        * Managed Databases Discover all our Managed Databases products
            
            * [Managed MongoDB](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/mongodb/) Document-oriented NoSQL engine. Try for free with Free Tier
            * [Managed MySQL](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/mysql/) Popular relational database that adapts to your usage
            * [Managed PostgreSQL](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/postgresql/) The top open-source relational database engine
            * [Managed Caching](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/redis/) More performance with our in-memory database, compatible with Redis™
            * [Managed Cassandra](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/apache-cassandra/) High availability service for high volumes of write requests
            * [Managed M3DB](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/m3db/) Track your metrics with an open-source time series platform
            * [Managed M3 Aggregator](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/m3-aggregator/) Aggregate your M3DB streams and integrate them directly into your workflows
            * Our Documentation View our documentation for the Databases range
            * En route to PaaS Focus on your applications & become more competitive
        * Back to menu
            
        * Containers & Orchestration Explore all our Containers & Orchestration products
            
            * [Managed Kubernetes Service](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/kubernetes/) Orchestrate your containerised applications with a CNCF-certified Kubernetes cluster
            * [Load Balancer for Managed Kubernetes Service](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/load-balancer-kubernetes/) Manage variations in activity by distributing traffic across multiple resources
            * [Managed Rancher Service New](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/managed-rancher-service/) Simplified and centralised management of your Kubernetes clusters
            * [Managed Private Registry](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/managed-private-registry/) Manage your images of containers and helmchart on a secure private registry
            * Our documentation View our documentation for the Containers & Orchestration range
            * En route to PaaS Focus on your applications & become more competitive
        * Back to menu
            
        * Data Analytics Explore all our Data Analytics products
            
            * [Managed Kafka](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/apache-kafka/) Queueing solution for deploying your event-driven architectures
            * [Kafka Connect](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/kafka-connect/) Extension simplifying the ingestion of your sources to Apache Kafka
            * [Kafka MirrorMaker](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/kafka-mirrormaker/) Replication ensuring high availability for your Kafka clusters
            * [Data Processing](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/data-processing/) Spark-as-a-Service for your massive data processing
            * [Logs Data Platform](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/identity-security-operations/logs-data-platform/) Complete platform to collect, store and view your logs
            * [Managed OpenSearch](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/opensearch/) A dedicated engine for indexing, searching and analyzing data
            * [Managed Dashboards](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/grafana/) Grafana® platform for creating dashboards
            * Our documentation View our documentation for the Data Analytics range
            * En route to PaaS Focus on your applications & become more competitive
        * Back to menu
            
        * Data Platform Browse all our Data Platform products
            
            * [Discover the OVHcloud Data Platform Beta](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/data-platform/) Carry out your Data & Analytics projects in record time and with ease
            * [Data Catalog Beta](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/data-catalog/) More than 50 connectors for all your data sources
            * [Lakehouse Manager Beta](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/lakehouse-manager/) Unified data warehouse and data lake storage, based on Apache Iceberg
            * [Data Processing Engine Beta](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/data-processing-engine/) Automate the execution and orchestration of your ETL/ELT workloads
            * [Analytics Manager Beta](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/analytics-manager/) Create your dashboards and launch your requests with the Trino engine
            * [Application Services Beta](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/applications-services/) SDK and serverless services to deploy your APIs and Data applications
        * Back to menu
            
        * AI & Machine Learning Explore all our AI & Machine learning products
            
            * [AI & Quantum Notebooks](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/ai-notebooks/) Launch your Jupyter or VS Code notebooks in the cloud, and choose from our native AI or quantum frameworks
            * [AI Training](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/ai-training/) Train your AI models
            * [AI Deploy](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/ai-deploy/) Deploy machine learning models & get your predictions
            * [AI Endpoints Alpha](https://labs.ovhcloud.com/en/ai-endpoints/) Enrich your applications with cutting-edge AI APIs
            * Our documentation Browse our documentation for the AI & Machine Learning range
            * En route to PaaS Focus on your applications & become more competitive
    * Quantum Computing
        * Back to menu
        * Quantum Computing
            
        * Quantum Computing
            
            * Quantum Notebooks Launch your Jupyter or VS Code notebooks in the cloud, and choose from our native AI or quantum frameworks
            * [What is Quantum computing?](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/learn/what-is-quantum-computing/) Learn more about the next accelerated computing revolution and how to develop today’s solutions with tomorrow’s quantum computers
        * Back to menu
            
        * Identity, Security & Operations Discover all our Identity, Security & Operations products
            
            * [Identity and Access Management (IAM)](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/identity-security-operations/identity-access-management/) Secure your access management and improve your productivity
            * [Logs Data Platform](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/identity-security-operations/logs-data-platform/) Complete platform to collect, store and view your logs
            * [Services Logs](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/identity-security-operations/service-logs/) Monitor the performance and security of your cloud environment
    * Back to menu
        
        * Back to menu
            
        * Hosted Private Cloud [Get started with Hosted Private Cloud](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/hosted-private-cloud/)
            
            * [VMware on OVHcloud](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/hosted-private-cloud/vmware/) Managed VMware solution for all enterprises
            * SecNumCloud qualified-VMware on OVHcloud ANSSI-qualified VMware Trusted Zone solution
            * [Veeam option for VMware backup](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/hosted-private-cloud/vmware/veeam-managed-backup/) The Veeam Managed Backup solution for backing up your virtual machines
            * [Zerto option for your VMware Disaster Recovery Plan](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/hosted-private-cloud/vmware/zerto/) Multi-site Disaster Recovery Plan solution for your VMware clusters
            * [Veeam Enterprise option for all your backups](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/veeam-enterprise/) A dedicated Veeam Backup Replication solution for all your backups
        * Solutions
            
            * Datacentre extension and migration
            * Hybrid and Multi-Cloud Solutions
            * Disaster recovery solutions
            * View all solutions
        * Back to menu
            
        * Hosted Private Cloud
            
            * [Nutanix on OVHcloud](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/hosted-private-cloud/nutanix/) Our scalable, ready-to-use Nutanix hyperconverged platform (HCI)
            * [HYCU for OVHcloud](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/hycu/) Simplify the backup and migration of your Nutanix workloads
            * [Veeam Enterprise for all your backups](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/veeam-enterprise/) A dedicated Veeam Backup Replication solution for all your backups
        * Use cases
            
            * Migrate and manage your data
            * Disaster Recovery Plan (DRP)
            * Hyperconvergence, Savings and Ecology
            * Disaster Recovery (DRaaS)
        * Back to menu
            
        * SAP HANA
            
            * SAP HANA on Private Cloud The solution that facilitates your SAP deployments in a sovereign cloud
        * Solutions
            
            * SAP on OVHcloud
    * Compliance and certifications
        * Back to menu
        * Compliance and certifications
            
        * Compliance and certifications Full list of standards and regulations
            
            * SecNumCloud ANSSI Security Visa Qualification
            * HDS and healthcare data hosting Hosting healthcare data in the UK and across Europe
            * HIPAA and HITECH Hosting healthcare data in the US
            * PCI DSS Financial data hosting
            * ISO/IEC 27001, 27017 and 27018 Information Security Management
            * ISO/IEC 27701 Managing the security of personal data processing
            * [ISO 50001](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/compliance/iso-50001/) Energy management
            * SOC 1, 2 and 3 AICPA SSAE 16/ISAE 3402 type II attestation and reports
            * EBA and ACPR Compliance for financial services operators in Europe
            * G-Cloud Public sector cloud service delivery in the UK
        * Back to menu
            
        * Network
            
            * [Additional IP](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/additional-ip/) Assign and move dynamic IP addresses from one service to another
            * [OVHcloud Load Balancer](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/load-balancer/) Balance your application load across multiple backend servers
            * [Private Network (vRack)](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/vrack/) Connect all your OVHcloud services together with an isolated private network
            * [OVHcloud Connect](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/ovhcloud-connect/) Connect your datacentre to OVHcloud
            * [Bring Your Own IP (BYOIP)](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/network/byoip/) Bring your IP addresses and simplify your migration to OVHcloud
        * Back to menu
            
        * Network Security
            
            * [Anti-DDoS infrastructure](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/security/anti-ddos/) Keep your infrastructures protected against DDoS attacks
            * [DNSSEC](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/domains/dnssec/) Protect your data from DNS cache poisoning
            * SSL Gateway Simplest way to enable security on your webpage. Without any effort!
    * Identity, Security & Operations
        * Back to menu
        * Identity, Security & Operations
            
        * Identity, Security & Operations
            
            * Identity and Access Management (IAM) Secure your access management and enhance your productivity
            * Logs Data Platform Complete platform to collect, store and view your logs
            * Service Logs Monitor your cloud environment’s performance and security
    * Back to menu
        
    * Use Cases
        
        * Back to menu
        * Use Cases
        * Use Cases
            
        * Back to menu
            
        * Industry
            
            * [Public Sector](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/industries/public-sector/) A trusted solution for governments and authorities
            * [Healthcare](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/industries/healthcare/) The trusted solution for the healthcare sector
            * [Financial Service](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/industries/financial-services/) Our solutions for financial services operators
            * [Manufacturing](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/industries/manufacturing/) The trusted cloud solution for European manufacturers
            * [Software/Information Technology](https://opentrustedcloud.ovhcloud.com/en/) SaaS and PaaS solutions from OVHcloud Partner Software Publishers
            * [Gaming](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/industries/gaming/) Cloud solutions for companies and individuals in the gaming industry
            * [Blockchain](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/industries/blockchain/) Free up your blockchain projects with OVHcloud solutions
    * Organisation Type
        
        * Back to menu
        * Organisation Type
        * Organisation Type
            
            * [Enterprise](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/enterprise/) Solutions for enterprise-level digital transformation
            * [Software publishers (SaaS/PaaS)](https://opentrustedcloud.ovhcloud.com/en/) SaaS and PaaS solutions from OVHcloud Partner Software Publishers
            * [System Integrator](https://partner.ovhcloud.com/en/) Solutions for integrators, service providers and consulting firms
            * [Government / Administrations](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/industries/public-sector/) Trusted solutions for governments and authorities
            * [Startup](https://startup.ovhcloud.com/en/startups/) Support solutions for start-ups
            * [Scaleup](https://startup.ovhcloud.com/en/scaleups/) Support solutions for scale-ups
    * Technology
        
        * Back to menu
        * Technology
        * Technology
            
            * [VMware by Broadcom](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/vmware/) VMware by Broadcom and OVHcloud solutions for all your projects
            * [Nutanix](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/nutanix/) Accelerate and simplify your hybrid multicloud journey with Nutanix on OVHcloud solution
            * [HYCU](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/storage-solutions/hycu/) The backup solution trusted by Nutanix users
            * [SAP](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/sap/) Our SAP on OVHcloud solutions for SAP environments hosting in a sovereign cloud
            * [NetApp](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/netapp/) NetApp storage solutions with cost control and high performance
            * [Nvidia](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/nvidia/) Nvidia GPU solutions for accelerating your innovation and AI projects
            * [MongoDB](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/mongodb/) MongoDB solutions that simplify data management
            * [OpenStack](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/public-cloud/openstack/) OpenStack solutions integrated with OVHcloud for cloud infrastructure
            * [Intel](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/dedicated-servers-intel/) Top-of-the-line cloud solutions powered by AMD processors
            * [AMD](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/bare-metal/dedicated-servers-amd/) Expert solutions powered by Intel® Xeon® that accelerate cloud processes
            * [Hadoop Cloudera](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/solutions/uc-big-data-managed-hadoop-clusters/) Your 100% managed Cloudera solution with Claranet
    * Back to menu
        
        Ecosystem [Discover the OVHcloud partner ecosystem](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/ecosystem/)
    * * [Partner Program](https://partner.ovhcloud.com/en/) An initiative dedicated to our reseller partners, integrators, administrators and consultants.
        * [Open Trusted Cloud](https://opentrustedcloud.ovhcloud.com/en/) An ecosystem of labelled SaaS and PaaS solutions, hosted in our open, reversible and reliable cloud
        * [Startup Program](https://startup.ovhcloud.com/en/) A support program for startups and scaleups to accelerate their growth
        * [OVHcloud Labs](https://labs.ovhcloud.com/en/) The innovation zone to test our cutting-edge technologies before they are officially launched on the market
        * [Our Ecosystem events](https://events.ovhcloud.com/en/) Find all the events dedicated to our partner ecosystem: webinars, conferences, and more
        * [Training & Certification](https://partner.ovhcloud.com/en/training-certification/) Develop your expertise with the training and certifications available to OVHcloud Partner Program members.
    * Quick Access
        
        * Sign up to the OVHcloud Startup Program
    * Back to menu
        
        About
    * * Who we are
        * Newsroom
        * Our datacenters
        * Our commitments
        * Innovation
        * Sustainable cloud
        * Trusted cloud

Open search bar

Close search bar

No result

Products

Solutions

Partners

Documentation

Articles

OVHcloud personal data usage policy
-----------------------------------

Privacy Policy
==============

* * *

* Privacy Policy

**Updated as of 29 January 2024**

At OVHcloud, protecting Personal Information is a key concern for us.  
  
As part of its activities, OVH Hosting Inc. and companies within the OVH Group, excluding entities located in theUnited States (hereinafter collectively “_OVHcloud_”), may be required to collect, use, disclose and store Personal Information about you (“_Concerned Person_”, “_you_”, "_your_”,).  
  
If you are an OVHcloud customer or prospective customer (hereinafter referred to as “_Customer(s)_”), or if you are an officer, employee, or employee of the latter (hereinafter referred to as “_Agent(s)_”), the purpose of this Privacy Policy is to describe the conditions under which OVHcloud manages your Personal Information, whether when using its products and services, its website, or contacts with its support service.  
  
This policy does not apply to the Personal Information that Clients entrust to OVHcloud in the context of using its services, including those hosted by Clients on infrastructure provided to them by OVHcloud. This information is only used and stored by OVHcloud as a service provider, on instruction from the Client, under the conditions set out in the Personal Information Protection Agreement.  
  
**What is personal information ?**  
  
Personal Information is any information about an individual that can be identified, directly or indirectly, inaccordance with the Act respecting the protection of personal information in the private sector in Quebec (CQLR, c.P-39.1), the "Quebec Privacy Act".  
  
This can be your surname, first name, postal or email address, but also an order or invoice number, or an IPaddress.

1. [Why does OVHcloud collect my Personal Information ?](#purposes)
2. [Where is the Personal Information collected by OVHcloud hosted ?](#storage)
3. [Destruction and anonymization](#protectionMeasures)
4. [Destruction et anonymisation](#anonymize)
5. [Who are the recipients of the Personal Information collected?](#recipients)
6. [Rights of data subjects](#personConcerned)

Why does OVHcloud collect my Personal Information ?
---------------------------------------------------

OVHcloud collects and uses the Personal Information of its Customers for the purposes of the activities described below. In this policy, the processing of Personal Information includes, but is not limited to, its use.

Personal Information is collected directly from you when you provide it to OVHcloud. This is the case, for example, if you send an email or fill out a web form, such as the customer account creation form. OVHcloud also collects Personal Information automatically on its websites and through analytical tools or digital markers. OVHcloud may use cookies in this connection. This Policy may also provide for other means by which Personal Information is collected.

1. [Contract Management](#contractManagement)
2. [Running OVHcloud services](#servicesExec)
3. [Customer Relationship Management](#customerRelation)
4. [Business Prospecting Management](#marketing)
5. [Enforcement Management](#fraudPrevention)
6. [Facilitating your future payments](#futurePayments)
7. [Collections Management](#recovery)
8. [Customer relationship management and improvement and statistical reporting](#stats)
9. [Site Customization](#website)
10. [Online targeted advertising](#advertising)
11. [Compliance with legal obligations](#mandatory)

### 1\. Contract Management

**Description of processing operations**  
OVHcloud processes Personal Information in the context of managing contracts concluded directly with its Customers and/or with partners. The Personal Information collected may relate to the Client and/or its Agents when the Client is a legal person or a partnership.

This Personal Information is used by OVHcloud to carry out the operations required to process orders, make services available, pay for   orders and subscriptions, and pay for related bills. Where applicable, such Personal Information may also be used for the delivery of products.

**Classes of Personal Information Processed**  
As part of managing contracts, OVHcloud is required to process the following Personal Information: 

* Identifying information, including:  surname, first name, postal and electronic contact information, phone number, identification document, proof of address;
* Login data for the OVHcloud Control Panel: login email address, password, OVHcloud NIC handle, IP address, login log, etc.;
* Payment data: bank card and/or bank account information;
* Tracking data for the business relationship: order history, order amount, and invoices.

### 2\. Running OVHcloud services

**Description of processing operations**

OVHcloud collects the Personal Information of its Customers and/or Agents in connection with the provision of its services and in order to ensure their maintenance.

**Types of Personal Information Processed**

* Customer and/or their Agents’ identification data:  surname, first name, contact details, customer ID and users, or “NIC Handle” of the Customer or its Agents;
* Communications between the Client and/or its Agents with OVHcloud: emails, support tickets relating to the provision and use of services, maintenance operations or any incidents;
* Information relating to the services used, including technical data: characteristics of the services, information relating to their use, and the Service’s location (as defined in the OVHcloud General Conditions), machine IDs, IP addresses, configurations, connection data, service statuses, usage data and event logs.

To the extent that OVHcloud autonomously determines the conditions of use of this Personal Information in its tools and information system, OVHcloud is the company that collects, holds, retains, uses and communicates this Personal Information.

Please note that some OVHcloud services are provided in collaboration with partners (such as domain name operators sold by OVHcloud, or software license providers) to whom Personal Information may be communicated with the aim of delivering the products or services concerned. In this case, the conditions under which the partner uses this Personal Information are set out in the specific conditions applicable to the services concerned.

### 3\. Customer Relationship Management

**Description of processing operations**  
OVHcloud collects Personal Information relating to its Customers and/or their Attendant(s) as part of the management of exchanges with its Customer Service in order to respond to requests for information, and any complaints.

OVHcloud may also process Personal Information for the purpose of constituting evidence in the context of a dispute or litigation with its Client and/or its Agents.

**Types of Personal Information Processed**

* Data identifying the Client and/or its Agents: name, first name, contact details, customer ID and users (“NIC Handle”) of the Client or its Agents;
* Information relating to the services used: characteristics of the services, information relating to their use, and the location of the Service, machine IDs, IP addresses, configurations, connection data, service statuses, usage data and event logs;
* Order, billing, and payment method information;
* Communications between the Client and/or their Agents and OVHcloud’s Client Service (exchanges such as media tickets relating to the conclusion and execution of the contract, request and response histories, telephone records where applicable);
* Personal Information on social media when customers or their agents contact us on these platforms;
* The set of items that the customer provides to support.

As part of customer relationship management, the Personal Information of OVH Hosting Inc. customers may be accessible to employees of OVH Group companies located within the European Union.

### 4\. Business Prospecting Management

**Description of processing operations**  
OVHcloud collects Personal Information about its Customers and/or their Agents in order to inform them about OVHcloud activities (and where applicable, its partners), the launch of new products and/or services, offer them services and/or offer them promotions, and/or invite them to OVHcloud events.

OVHcloud uses the Personal Information collected for the purposes of the uses described above only after obtaining the express, free and informed consent of the data subject.

OVHcloud may also contact individuals for marketing purposes who have expressed their consent to receive communications from OVHcloud with OVHcloud partners. In this context, OVHcloud partners collect the Personal Information required to send communications, as well as the consent of the person concerned. OVHcloud ensures that their Personal Information and consent to commercial prospecting has been collected in accordance with applicable laws.

**Categories of Personal Information Used**

* Customer and/or their Agents’ identification data: first name, last name, contact details, email address;
* Internet browsing data: IP address, user ID, browsing history on OVH websites;
* Interests of the Client and/or its Agents: data relating to the use of services, order history, consumption habits, participation in events;
* Customer and/or their agents’ interactions with OVHcloud.

### 5\. Enforcement Management

**Description of processing operations**  
   
OVHcloud uses the Personal Information of its Customers and, where applicable,their Agents to ensure the security of payments, and to detect and prevent fraud. Assuch, OVHcloud has also implemented an optional multi-factor authentication feature to enhance the security of your account. As part of this use, Personal Information may be transferred to OVHcloud’s Fraud Prevention Team located in France and Quebec, or to Customer Relationship Teams in France and Quebec regarding a request related to your multi-factor authentication. 

**Categories of Personal Information Used**

* Customer and/or their Agents’ identification data: name, surname, contact details,email address, postal address, province, city, country;
* Payment data: information relating to the bank card and/or bank account;  
    Connection data: IP address;
* Tracking data of the business relation: order history, order amount, invoices and, if applicable, outstanding amount;
* Location data.

In some cases, OVHcloud may be required to request the following documents:

* Customer or their representative’s identification document;
* proof of address;
* Certificate of registration of a business;
* Authority of the leader;
* Bank details.

### 6\. Facilitating your future payments

**Description of processing operations**  
OVHcloud holds, stores and uses the Personal Information of its Customers relating to their payment method(s) in connection with the subscription by its Customers to a service with automatic renewal or when the Customer has expressed their wish to save their credit card on their customer account in order to facilitate their subsequent payments.

**Categories of Personal Information Used**

* Customer and/or their Agents’ identification data: surname, first name, email address;
* Bank card data: first 6 digits (relating to the bank that issued the card) and last 4 digits of the bank card or IBAN

### 7\. Collections Management

**Description of processing operations**

OVHcloud uses the Personal Information of its Customers and/or Agents to identify unpaid orders and enable the recovery of outstanding amounts.

**Categories of Personal Information Used**

* Identification data: surname, first name, email address, postal address;
* Billing data: payment methods, bank details, order history, order amount, invoices and any outstanding amounts.

When using Personal Information for collection purposes, OVHcloud may transfer Personal Information to collection service providers and external advisors.

### 8\. Customer relationship management and improvement and statistical reporting

**Description of processing operations**  
OVHcloud collects Personal Information relating to its Customers and/or their Agents, as appropriate, as part of the management of the management and improvement of the customer relationship, in order to develop statistical reports to evaluate the overall satisfaction related to OVHcloud products.

**Classes of Personal Information Processed**

* Information relating to the services used: characteristics of the services, information relating to their use, and the location of the Service, machine IDs, IP addresses, configurations, connection data, service statuses, usage data and event logs;
* Any data communicated by Customers and/or their Agents (if applicable) as part of the satisfaction questionnaire sent by OVHcloud

As part of managing customer relationship improvements and for the purposes of improving OVHcloud services, the Personal Information of OVHcloud Hosting Inc. Customers and/or their Agents may be accessible to employees of OVHcloud Group companies located within the European Union.

### 9\. Site Customization

The Personal Information collected for the customization of OVHcloud websites, as well as its use, is described in our [Cookies Policy](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/terms-and-conditions/cookies-policy/)

### 10\. Online targeted advertising

The personal information collected for online advertising related to your browsing on OVHcloud websites is indicated in our [Cookies Policy](https://www.ovhcloud.com/en/terms-and-conditions/cookies-policy/)

### 11\. Compliance with legal obligations

**Description of processing operations**  
As part of its business, OVHcloud is subject to various legal obligations, compliance with which requires the collection, use, communication and storage of Personal Information.

OVHcloud’s legal obligations include complying with tax and accounting obligations, processing requests to exercise the rights of data subjects using Personal Information, responding to certain requests from courts, judicial or administrative authorities for the provision of information, and declaring certain incidents of confidentiality.

When OVHcloud receives requests from judicial, administrative or other authorities to disclose Personal Information in its possession, it agrees to:

* Check the competence of the requesting authority;
* Only respond to validly formed requests;
* If authorized, inform the data subject in advance in order to enable them to assert their rights;
* Limit disclosure to only Personal Information required by the authority.

**Classes of Personal Information Processed**

* Regarding compliance with tax and accounting obligations: all information related to orders and related invoices;
* With respect to requests to exercise rights: all of the Personal Information that is the subject of the request;
* With regard to requests from courts, judicial or administrative authorities: all of the Personal Information requested.

Where is the Personal Information collected by OVHcloud hosted ?
----------------------------------------------------------------

**Hosting Personal Information**  
The Personal Information covered by this policy is hosted in Quebec in a datacentre owned and operated by OVHcloud.

If a customer chooses to use OVHcloud services in datacentres located outside of Canada (including the European Union, Singapore, India, or Australia), Personal Information necessary to perform the services may be hosted in the respective country.

**Remote Access**  
Uses of Personal Information as well as occasional communications of Personal Information may be made outside of Quebec and/or Canada due to OVHcloud’s international dimension. As a result, companies within the OVH Group may participate in the use of the Customer’s Personal Information outside of Quebec and Canada.

When a disclosure of Personal Information outside of Quebec and/or Canada occurs, OVHcloud implements technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information between members of the OVHcloud Group in accordance with applicable laws.

Personal Information security measures
--------------------------------------

La protection des Renseignements Personnels est pleinement intégrée au système de gestion de sécurité de l’information d’OVHcloud, dans le cadre duquel OVHcloud poursuit différents objectifs tels que :

* Déploiement d’une approche industrielle, à grand échelle de la sécurité ;
* Positionnement d’OVHcloud comme un acteur de confiance dans l’écosystème numérique ;
* Mise en place de systèmes de management de la sécurité (ISMS) et de la vie privée (PIMS) ;
* Approche de la sécurité par les risques ;
* Démonstration de la sécurité via les certifications, le contrôle interne et l’audit externe ;
* Réponse unifiée aux incidents de sécurité et aux incidents de confidentialité ;
* Intégration des enjeux de sécurité de protection de la vie privée dans l’évolution des produits ;
* Évaluation de la sécurité et mise en place d’amélioration continue.

Par ailleurs, OVHcloud garantit que ses salariés autorisés à avoir accès à des Renseignements Personnels sont soumis à une obligation de confidentialité et reçoivent une formation appropriée concernant la protection des Renseignements Personnels.

Destruction and anonymization
-----------------------------

OVHcloud reserves the right to anonymise the Personal Information that is the subject of this policy, i.e. to modify it so that it no longer directly or indirectly identifies, individualizes or singles the data subject, and to reuse it only in anonymous form.

OVHcloud strives to apply the following anonymization principles:

* The impossibility of isolating an individual within a larger group based on the data;
* The inability to link two records about the same person; and
* The impossibility of inferring, with a high probability, unknown information about a person.

OVHcloud reserves the right to store and use this anonymised data for other legitimate, serious purposes than those set out in this policy, including producing statistics, developing new or improved services, conducting marketing analyzes, and developing business strategies.

Who are the recipients of the Personal Information collected ?
--------------------------------------------------------------

Les Renseignements Personnels collectés sont utilisés par le personnel d’OVH Hébergement Inc.  
Nous veillons à ce que seules les personnes habilitées au sein de cette société puissent accéder aux renseignements personnels et uniquement lorsque cela est nécessaire à l’exécution de leurs missions.

Nous pouvons également être amenés à communiquer vos Renseignements Personnels à : 

* des sociétés du Groupe OVHcloud, à l’exception des entités se situant aux Etats-Unis, dans le cadre de l’exécution des utilisations mentionnées à l’article II de la présente politique.
* des prestataires tiers tels que des prestataires de services de sécurité, fournisseurs réseaux, fournisseurs d’applications et d’outils internes, prestataires de services de paiement, fournisseurs de solutions de courriels, enquêtes de satisfaction.

OVHcloud s’assure que ses fournisseurs de services s’engagent à respecter les lois applicables en matière de protection des Renseignements Personnels et mettent en place des mesures de protection des Renseignements Personnels appropriées. 

OVHcloud veille notamment à ce que ces fournisseurs de servicesn’aient accès qu’aux seuls Renseignements Personnels nécessaires à l’exécution de leur mission.

Rights of data subjects
-----------------------

In accordance with applicable laws, data subjects have the right to access their Personal Information, as well as the right to rectify it and request its deletion and portability. Where the use, retention and disclosure of Personal Information is based on the consent of the individual concerned, the individual has the right to withdraw that consent at any time. 

These rights may be exercised by mail to the following address: Privacy Officer, OVH Hosting Inc., 1801 McGill College Avenue, Suite 800, Montréal, Quebec H3A 2N4 Canada.

They can also be exercised using the email address rprp@ovh.ca. You may be asked to provide proof of identity to confirm your identity. This part will be deleted immediately after your request is processed.

In compliance with applicable laws, each request must be accompanied by information that can demonstrate the identity of the requestor. They shall be replied to as soon as possible and in any event within 30 days of receipt. In the event of reasonable doubt as to the identity of the person making the request, additional information necessary to confirm the identity of the person concerned, including the presentation of proof of identity, may be requested.

The person with the highest authority within OVHcloud has delegated the role of Personal Information Protection Officer to the OVHcloud Data Protection Officer. You can contact this person, to exercise your rights and in the event of any complaint, at the address mentioned above. 

OVHcloud will investigate any complaints about your Personal Information and, if warranted, take appropriate action to correct the situation. This complaint shall be answered as soon as possible and, where possible, within 30 days of receipt. In the event of dissatisfaction with the internal review of your complaint, the person concerned may contact the Commission d’accès à l’information du Québec or the Office of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada, or any other authority with jurisdiction over privacy matters.

Back to top

* Tools
    
    * My customer account
    * Webmail
    * API
    * Status
    * Domain contact
    * Report abuse (abuse@ovh.net)

* Support

* Contact us
    
    New order, technical advice, incidents  
    OVHcloud Customer Service
    
    **1-855-684-5463**
    
    Toll free

* News
    
    * Press
    * Blog
    
* Social networks
    
    * * 
        * 
        * 
        * 
        * 
        * 
        * 

* Keep in touch

* Legal notices
* Contracts
* Rights and obligations of domain name holders
* ICANN documentation for domain name holders
* Payments
* About OVHcloud
* OVHcloud Careers
